James Ahn

portfolio / jamesahn.co

ux/ui designer jamesahn0717@gmail.com

linkedin.com/in/james-ahn (236)-512-9610

Summary of Skills

UX Design HTML Photoshop **Teamwork UI** Design CSS Illustrator Problem Solving Prototyping Python Premiere Pro Time Management Figma InDesign Lightroom Balsamiq

1 year + of key experience in the travel industry, combined with a solid academic background specializing in user experience

2 years + of prototyping and design sprints for quick ideas

3 years + of working in Figma with teammates and efficiently got work done with them in an effective pace

Experience

Business and Design Mentor - StarterHacks at University of Waterloo

Jan 2020

Mentored students participating in StarterHacks (Canada's largest

beginner-focused hackathon) with potential routes and tactics on executing with a balanced business model

Used advantage of my dual background in business and design to apply real world concepts to fledgling projects that needed fleshing out

UX/UI Design Intern - Tugolo

May 2019 - August 2019

Re-designed Tugolo's entire web interface using Figma to make the user-end experience more interactive and accessible

Took control of the mobile platform design, a key part of the company's target group, while working in a 5-person team of one other designer and three developers

Implemented wireframes and high-fidelity models, compiling user feedback and testing closely with other employees

UX/UI Designer - Tastebuds

Jan 2020 - present

Leading the design responsibility for a start-up, making adjustments on the current interface to present a more simple and intuitive look

Highly involved in designing the user's profile and statistics of their progress with and motivated by user feedback

Education

Honours Global Business and Digital Arts — University of Waterloo

Sept 2017 - April 2021

Exchange Program - Singapore University of Technology and Design

Sept 2019 - Dec 2019

Activities & Interests

Snowboarding Camping Hiking Travelling

Photography Videography

Snowboarding

Participated in the snowboarding club in my high school and went to provincials and won 3rd place boys snowboarding and 1st place in mixed snowboarding

Travelling

Went on exchange to Singapore and travelled to 5 different countries, adding count to the 21 countries I've travelled to

Continuously expanding my knowledge through experiencing different cultures